<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ben Sanders</title>
    <description>Ben Sanders is an all-around Geek and loves to write about the latest technology/gaming news. If you want a personal take on technology and gaming news come have a read. 
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:50:15 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 10:50:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>.Life Update</title>
        <description>&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc-2018-evento-san-jose.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;
    
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;


</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/life-update-november-2018/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/life-update-november-2018/</guid>
        
        <category>thebensanders,</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>life,</category>
        
        <category>update,</category>
        
        <category>privacy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple WWDC 2018</title>
        <description>&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc-2018-evento-san-jose.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;
    It's that time again for another Apple WWDC and I'm going to attempt to live blog the event here.
    You will need to refresh the page though since I'm using Jekyll but hey it's something to try. Please
    bear with me here.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Giving some Windows XP vibes with that wallpaper but a dark mode is always nice. 
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-macos-dark-mode.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Finally being able to open links on Apple Watch, for a quick preview at least.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-links-watchos.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    That's a cool feature. I can see that being nice for some quick communication.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-walkie-talkie.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Automatic workouts will be nice so that I can know what it counts as working out.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-automatic-work-watchos.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Some new stuff for those who are competitive in WatchOS 5. That's a nice feature to keep everyone active.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-group-facetime.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Group Facetime up to 32 people! That's is so cool and a nice addition to messages.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-ipad-update.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-ar.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    That's pretty cool with their focus on AR. Can't wait to get a chance to play with it myself.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-siri-refinements.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    That's interesting some siri shortcuts in search. That will be very helpful!
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-dnd-update.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Nice that they are giving some love to DND. Which is a must needed thing.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-group-notifications.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    That's a nice feature. Group notifications!
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/wwdc/apple-wwdc-memoji.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    That's cool and will probably be the killer of bitmoji. Maybe the last nail in the coffin
    for Snapchat?
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;


</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/apple-wwdc-june-2018/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/apple-wwdc-june-2018/</guid>
        
        <category>thebensanders,</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>apple,</category>
        
        <category>wwdc,</category>
        
        <category>june,</category>
        
        <category>privacy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Share Only What You Want Out There</title>
        <description>&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/AdobeStock_Privacy_Small.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Since I graduated back in 2011 I suppose I was one of the last group of high-schoolers
    to know what life was like before the proliferation of social media. One thing you
    have to keep in mind when sharing on the internet, let alone social media, is that
    once you put it out there. You have to assume it will always be there even if you 'delete' it.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    For example, at one point when I was going to school for web design and development,
    I was looking into building a social network. Granted it was mostly to practice coding
    but I was still interested in building one. I did some research on how other social
    media websites handled things like 'deleting' images and posts. One thing I found out
    was that it doesn't actually 'delete' it just sort of hides it.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    I'm sure that it eventually does get deleted and is gone but by the time you
    hit the delete button. You never know who has downloaded it and possibly shared
    it somewhere else. Which is the point of this article is to say that if you want to
    share something think it through first.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    To tie up this article with a nice bow, I will say that the whole Facebook/Cambridge
    Analytica thing made me want to write this article. From a programmer/web developer
    perspective, I see the issue being caused both by Facebook and the users being careless.
    The users that got their information leaked because they used Facebook to login to random
    apps for quizzes. Facebook for not doing more to protect that data.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Moral of the story is just be more careful what you share online. If you do
    share more personal information online don't use Facebook to login to those
    personality quizzes.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Thanks for reading and stay safe out there. :)
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/share-only-what-you-want-out-there/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/share-only-what-you-want-out-there/</guid>
        
        <category>thebensanders,</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>facebook,</category>
        
        <category>Cambridge Analytica,</category>
        
        <category>twitter,</category>
        
        <category>privacy</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Let's Talk About Sub4Sub</title>
        <description>&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/sub4sub.jpg&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;
    Since I started uploading more frequently to YouTube I have come across more
    people asking for sub4sub. The main problem with sub4sub is that, yes it gets
    you tons of subs, but you don't get actual views and watch time. You also end
    up with a bunch of subscriptions that you will probably never watch yourself.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    When it comes to getting people to subscribe to your channel you should want
    them to subscribe because you offer some kind of value to them. That value can
    come in the form of entertainment, education, or whatever else you might offer.
    That's why you should be doing a call-to-action at the end of your videos inviting
    viewers to subscribe, like, and/or comment. Doing that kind of reminds people that
    they can do all those things on YouTube.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    It may seem to take a lot longer to grow a channel without sub4sub but if you
    don't take part in that sub4sub culture. You will be able to find your niche on
    YouTube that will allow you to grow your channel. That just simply doesn't happen
    with sub4sub because it just gets a bunch of people subscribed that will probably
    only last at most a month.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    More recently I posted a link to my channel in a blogs comment section which
    got about 8 subs from. The problem was people commented saying &quot;subbed, now sub back&quot;.
    Well as you can imagine once I didn't sub back all 8 unsubbed. That shows that they
    weren't actually interested in my content they just wanted to inflate their own sub count.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/sub4sub-graph.png&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    All-in-all sub4sub is a pretty terrible way to grow a channel and I'll leave
    you with a video on the topic. That being said if you want to watch my content
    and subscribe to me because of that you can find my channel here. &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://youtube.com/thebensanders/&quot;&gt;https://youtube.com/thebensanders/&lt;/a&gt;.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Thanks for reading, have a great day! :)
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section class=&quot;videoContent&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;525&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/VMbngWvulAg&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/about-sub-4-sub/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/about-sub-4-sub/</guid>
        
        <category>thebensanders,</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>sub4sub,</category>
        
        <category>sub,</category>
        
        <category>YouTube,</category>
        
        <category>Roberto Blake</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Sims 4 Laundry Day</title>
        <description>&lt;section class=&quot;videoContent&quot;&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;525&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/j8yTBEBpZts&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;
    So, it's finally here or at least tomorrow it will finally be here. The Sims
    4 Laundry Day stuff pack. Perhaps the first stuff pack I can remember I have
    been excited about. I think the main reason I'm excited about this stuff pack
    is that it is the first time the community has voted on what the next stuff
    pack will be. Maybe if this pack ends up being a success it will lead them to
    work with the community in future TS4 content.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    I'm a simmer, that's one thing that is for sure. I've been playing The Sims
    franchise since my dad bought the first game for my mom. I can remember
    spending hours as a kid playing the game. It's one of the main game franchises
    that shaped my childhood. Perhaps I'll do a video or a blog post on games I
    played as a child in the future.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    So, what are my thoughts on the actual stuff pack getting ready to come out?
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    I love it! The reason being that back when laundry was first introduced back
    in The Sims 3: Ambitions I loved watching my Sims do laundry. There's just
    something about laundry, and seasons, that adds more realism to the game.
    It makes it easier for me to put myself in that world.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    There's also the trailer they made for the stuff pack which I can tell The
    Sims team was having fun. Although considering the topic of the stuff pack.
    I'm surprised they were able to make the trailer as exciting as it is.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    I'm looking forward to putting another 300 hours into the game or, you know,
    something like that. I'll emerge on the other side not knowing what's going
    on in the real world. Perhaps even mainly speaking in Similish.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Let me know in the comments if you are looking forward to The Sims 4: Laundry
    Day Stuff! I look forward to your thoughts. You can follow me on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/thebensanders&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt; and
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtube.com/thebensanders&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt; as well as subscribe to my blog. Thanks for reading and have a great
    day. Happy Siming.
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/the-sims-4-laundry-day/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-sims-4-laundry-day/</guid>
        
        <category>thebensanders,</category>
        
        <category>2018</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>the sims 4,</category>
        
        <category>TS4,</category>
        
        <category>Laundry Day,</category>
        
        <category>TS4 Laundry Day,</category>
        
        <category>The Sims 4 Laundry Day,</category>
        
        <category>Electronic Arts</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Read More.</title>
        <description>&lt;section class=&quot;photoset&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/read-more-small.jpg&quot; class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; alt=&quot;Google Drive Logo&quot;&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;
    I can remember the very first book I read all the way through. It was &quot;Harry
    Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone&quot;.  I remember the day I decided to start
    reading the Harry Potter Series. It was right after I had seen the first film.
    I guess I wanted to be immersed in the Harry Potter universe even more.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Ever since those days though I haven't really read a whole lot other than
    the occasional blog posts. Which, I suppose, is still reading and you can
    still get the same benefits as reading a book. I just haven't taken the time
    to just sit back, relax, and take a journey with a nice book in a while.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    You see since the start of 2018 I have been thinking about reading more.
    Well, not just reading more but writing more as well. I am aware that I wrote
    several posts in 2017. I just want to try to write much longer, more meaningful
    blog posts. Sort of like short stories but on the web. Carefully crafting a
    story that would take the reader on an adventure with each and every word.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    I want to try to take my writing to the next level by taking the reader on a
    journey in their own mind. Sort of the way a good book does when you sit down
    to read it. Like how you start imagining what that world would be like to
    live in.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    I'm going to stray a little here to say that I have been trying to find my
    niche on YouTube. I had recently found the BookTube community which seems to
    go with what I want to do in terms of reading and writing more. Hell, I might
    even actually write a novel one day. Wouldn't that be great?
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    So, where is this all going, I hear you ask yourself.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Well, here in 2018 I would honestly like to read more. Starting with Emma
    Blackery's &quot;Feel Good 101&quot;. I don't like setting a certain number but I'm
    going to say I'd like to read 20 books in 2018. Mostly books I already own
    which include: Egghead and The Fault in Our Stars.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;Why Read Though?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Some people might say something about how you can get the same relaxation
    from watching TV or a YouTube video. The problem with that thinking though
    is that it still requires you to stare at a screen. I love the idea that
    reading allows you to put away your computer and phone for a small, to large,
    amount of time.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    While you can read on, say an iPad, you've still got the notifications
    coming through interrupting your reading. I want to read because it's a way
    to fully escape the world into a whole different one. Even reading non-fiction
    books can help you escape. It can conjure up what it must have been like to live
    in the times that book is talking about.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    I like the way that Paul Stamatiou worded it on his
    &lt;a href=&quot;https://paulstamatiou.com/reading-more-kindle-oasis/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;blog&lt;/a&gt;.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    &quot;Reading forces you to go one step further and not even let your mind wander
    a bit. If it does, you're punished by having to read the paragraph or page
    over again to understand what’s happening&quot;
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    That's very true I can attest to have been reading a book and my mind started
    wondering about something else. Then next thing I knew I was lost and didn't
    know where I had left off.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Reading isn't just about relaxing though it also allows you to see things
    from a different perspective. If you are set in your beliefs on one thing
    reading can give you a new perspective on those beliefs. You may or may not
    change what you personally believe but at least you have a better understanding
    of someone else's point-of-view.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;What to read?&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    As I've mentioned above I'm starting out with Emma Blackery's book since
    that is the most recent book I bought. I do have several books in mind that
    I have been meaning to read myself. One book is &quot;Steve Jobs&quot; by Walter Isaacson.
    I will also be keeping an eye on Bill Gate's, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatesnotes.com/&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gatesnotes&lt;/a&gt;, blog for ideas on
    books to read.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    Thankfully, as mentioned previously, I found the
    &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/results?search_query=booktube&quot;&gt;BookTube community&lt;/a&gt; which
    led me to make a &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/76373017-ben-sanders&quot;&gt;Goodreads account&lt;/a&gt;.
    So, that's another place I'm sure I'll find great books to read. Really,
    there should be no excuse for me not to read 20 books in 2018.
  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
    My final thoughts are that I'm hoping I can actually read 20, or more, books
    in 2018. I'm sure it will lead to me having a greater knowledge of the world
    and ultimately help improve my writing. Who knows? Perhaps by November of this
    year, I will actually participate in NaNoWriMo and have a published novel. :)
  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/read-more/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/read-more/</guid>
        
        <category>read more,</category>
        
        <category>thebensanders,</category>
        
        <category>Harry Potter,</category>
        
        <category>Emma Blackery,</category>
        
        <category>2018</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>2017</category>
        
        <category>reading,</category>
        
        <category>Bo Burnham,</category>
        
        <category>Egghead,</category>
        
        <category>Paul Stamatiou,</category>
        
        <category>BookTube,</category>
        
        <category>Book Tube,</category>
        
        <category>reading plus answers level h,</category>
        
        <category>why reading is important,</category>
        
        <category>books to read,</category>
        
        <category>books to read online</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Webms Are Cool</title>
        <description>&lt;!-- &lt;section class=&quot;photoset&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/NaNoWriMo_small.jpg&quot; class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; alt=&quot;Google Drive Logo&quot;&gt;
&lt;/section&gt; --&gt;
&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
  &lt;video autoplay loop=&quot;true&quot; src=&quot;/Videos/Jazza Flips Benjamin off.webm&quot; width=&quot;100%'&gt;&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/webms-are-cool/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/webms-are-cool/</guid>
        
        <category>webm,</category>
        
        <category>thebensanders,</category>
        
        <category>drawwithjazza,</category>
        
        <category>jazza,</category>
        
        <category>vs,</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>2017</category>
        
        <category>gif</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>National Novel Writing Month</title>
        <description>&lt;section class=&quot;photoset&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/NaNoWriMo_small.jpg&quot; class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; alt=&quot;Google Drive Logo&quot;&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I was listening to Not Too Deep with Grace Helbig and it was mentioned that
  November is National Novel Writing Month. My first thought was that I should blog about it. (lol)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Seriously though I have thought about writing a novel in the past.
  As I'm sure almost every single person in the world has thought about doing.
  I think I'll stick to writing more on my blog to help work on my writing and storytelling skills.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I would imagine that difference between writing a novel and a blog post would
  be that you can't just have short paragraphs. I don't know, maybe you can.
  In writing, there are certain rules you should follow but I imagine if you can
  tell a compelling story. You can write however you want.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  As with any creative skill, however, it just takes practice to get better at.
  You just have to pick a skill you feel you would enjoy and just do it.
  You will suck at first but eventually, if you keep at it you will find your own style.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
The worst thing for any writer is a blank page and there are plenty of remedies
to cure that problem. One of the main ones that many English college professors
will have you do is just write. Write about things and don't worry about grammar
or spelling. You can always edit it for grammar letter.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Thanks as always for taking the time to read my blog posts. I'm going to try to
post more during November and onwards. I just never really had much that I felt
I could add to the blogosphere. Hopefully, this post does add something and I
would love to hear from you, dear reader, in the comments below. :)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
PS: After I copy and pasted these &quot;paragraphs&quot; into Atom the article seemed a lot shorter then it did in Grammarly.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/national-novel-writing-month/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/national-novel-writing-month/</guid>
        
        <category>national novel writing month,</category>
        
        <category>thebensanders,</category>
        
        <category>writing,</category>
        
        <category>november,</category>
        
        <category>month,</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>2017</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Reasons To Upload Your Resume To Google Drive</title>
        <description>&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  So, you're out of school or are almost out and you are looking for a job?
  You've got your resume in hand or I should say in PDF form on your computer.
  You could upload it every time you send an email to a potential job or, and I
  suppose this only works if you use Gmail, you could upload it to Google Drive.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Recently I had applied for a job and I went to upload my resume to send to
  them and I had this thought about importing it from Google Drive. For some
  reason, all the times I had sent applications in I hadn't thought about doing
  this. I guess it's just me being stuck in the past so to speak. After I had
  sent the email I did think about the ease of which it would be to update my
  resume that company has now. If I update that one then it would just update
  for them since I basically sent them a link and allowed them to view it.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  So, my 5 reasons for uploading your resume to Google Drive and I suppose, as
  mentioned, this only applies if you use Gmail.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;ul class=&quot;in-post-list&quot;&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;1. Ease of Editability&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;2. Literally, only one copy is needed&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;3. &quot;The Cloud&quot; allows for access on any device&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;4. Importing is easy from inside Gmail&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;5. Super convenient&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Ease of Editability is as I mentioned above just the fact that you can edit the
  one file and have it update for all possible jobs. So, if you found a mistake
  when you sent the email you can quickly update it and have it reflected
  immediately.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  What I mean by &quot;literally, only one copy is needed&quot; is just as it sounds.
  You only need one copy since it's online in Google Drive you don't have to
  worry about resaving a Word Document as a PDF anymore. Just send the Google
  Drive Document, or whatever they call it.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &quot;The Cloud&quot;, which is a word I sort of hate since it simplifies the web a
  little too much but that's the buzz word that's been chosen. Either way
  &quot;The Cloud&quot; allows for you to view your resume, or any other document, on any
  device that has the app. So, if you need to show your resume to someone in a
  pinch just get your phone out and show them. You can even edit it from your
  phone, tablet, what have you.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Importing it from inside of Gmail is easy by just hitting the Drive icon and
  selecting your file. I would say it couldn't be any easier.
  I'll just include this last one in this paragraph. The last one being that
  it's just super convenient. Super convenient for really all the above points
  I mentioned.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Thanks for taking the time to read this post and be sure to share it if you
  want to and comment below with your thoughts. :)

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Until Next Time,
  - Ben Sanders
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/5-reasons-to-upload-your-resume-to-google-drive/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/5-reasons-to-upload-your-resume-to-google-drive/</guid>
        
        <category>5 reasons to upload your resume to google drive,</category>
        
        <category>5 reasons,</category>
        
        <category>resume,</category>
        
        <category>google,</category>
        
        <category>drive,</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>2017</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Using Font Awesome In 2017</title>
        <description>&lt;img class=&quot;post-featured-image&quot; src=&quot;/images/font-awesome-post-image.png&quot;&gt;
&lt;section class=&quot;storyContent&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  It has come to my attention that I should move into the new age so to speak of
  web development. I managed to teach myself SASS and get better with GIT, ha get,
  all jokes aside I need to keep my skills up. So, over the next few days, weeks
  and even months I'll be implementing &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://fontawesome.io/&quot;&gt;Font Awesome&lt;/a&gt; into my site.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I've always had trouble with things like the Hamburger menu, I guess because I
  always tried using an image for it. You know instead of using a CSS Icon Set.
  I'll also be trying to blog the experience more so I can get some actual
  content on this site.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I've already started filling out my &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://bensanders.me/portfolio&quot;&gt;portfolio&lt;/a&gt;.
  Although it's mostly just
  designs that I made up in Photoshop. I've also popped open Illustrator to make
  some logos but I don't feel they are that great to share yet. I mostly just
  keep trying to slog away to keep busy on something creative.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  I do still run my &lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-youtube-play&quot; aria-hidden=&quot;true&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://youtube.com/thebensanders&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;
  channel as well where I upload vlogs and short
  Overwatch clips. I have already uploaded more videos this year than all of
  last year put together and depending on if the Dragon Con trip works out I'll
  have that on my channel. Along with plenty of photos from the Con on this site.

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Whatever happens, the next 5 and a half months thank you for taking the time
  to read this little update post. That all it seems I ever do on this site
  anymore. (lol)

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Until Next Time, peace!&lt;br /&gt;
  - Ben Sanders &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  P.S. If you enjoyed this post don't forget to share it on all the socials
  and comment below! I looke forward to conversing with you all in the comments.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/using-font-awesome-in-2017/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/using-font-awesome-in-2017/</guid>
        
        <category>font awesome,</category>
        
        <category>Ben Sanders,</category>
        
        <category>2017</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
